<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Epstein Exposed</title>
    <link>https://epstein-exposed.com</link>
    <description>Comprehensive coverage of the Jeffrey Epstein DOJ file releases. In-depth analysis of documents, emails, and court records.</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <item>
      <title>Apollo CEO Leon Black Paid Epstein $158 Million for 'Tax Advice' - DOJ Files Reveal Shocking Details</title>
      <link>https://epstein-exposed.com/leon-black-apollo-payments.html</link>
      <guid>https://epstein-exposed.com/leon-black-apollo-payments.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 16:25:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>Billionaire Leon Black paid Jeffrey Epstein $158 million over five years for alleged tax and estate planning advice, new DOJ documents reveal.</description>
    </item>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://epstein-exposed.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>

    <item>
      <title>"What Day Will Be the Wildest Party?" Elon Musk's Desperate Texts to Epstein Exposed</title>
      <link>https://epstein-exposed.com/musk-epstein-emails</link>
      <guid>https://epstein-exposed.com/musk-epstein-emails</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>The world's richest man spent years trying to score an invite to Epstein's private island—and the receipts are mortifying. Buried in the 3.5 million pages are at least 16 emails between Musk and the convicted pedophile.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Steve Bannon Got a Free Apple Watch, Private Planes, and Hundreds of Texts from Epstein</title>
      <link>https://epstein-exposed.com/bannon-epstein-texts</link>
      <guid>https://epstein-exposed.com/bannon-epstein-texts</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Trump's former strategist was chatting up the sex trafficker right until weeks before his death—and Epstein knew exactly what he had on them both.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Commerce Secretary Lutnick Brought His Kids to Epstein's Island on a Yacht</title>
      <link>https://epstein-exposed.com/lutnick-yacht-island</link>
      <guid>https://epstein-exposed.com/lutnick-yacht-island</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2026 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Howard Lutnick's story just completely fell apart. Emails show his wife coordinated a Christmas visit on their 188-foot yacht—seven years after he claims he stopped associating with Epstein.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>The Dinner Party: Prince Andrew, Woody Allen, Katie Couric—All at Epstein's House</title>
      <link>https://epstein-exposed.com/prince-andrew-dinner</link>
      <guid>https://epstein-exposed.com/prince-andrew-dinner</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>A December 2010 email reveals the disgraced royal was staying at the convicted pedophile's Manhattan mansion while A-listers were invited over for dinner.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>"32 Plane Trips": The Clinton-Epstein Connection in Black and White</title>
      <link>https://epstein-exposed.com/clinton-plane-trips</link>
      <guid>https://epstein-exposed.com/clinton-plane-trips</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Internal emails show Epstein's team tracking and discussing the former president's extensive flight history on the "Lolita Express."</description>
    </item>

  </channel>
</rss>
