<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Epstein Files Daily</title>
    <link>https://epsteinfilesdaily.com</link>
    <description>Daily news roundups covering the Jeffrey Epstein DOJ file releases.</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://epsteinfilesdaily.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <item>
      <title>February 16: Bondi Claims All Epstein Files Released as Critics Demand More</title>
      <link>https://epsteinfilesdaily.com/daily-feb-16-2026.html</link>
      <guid>https://epsteinfilesdaily.com/daily-feb-16-2026.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 11:27:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>Pam Bondi Attorney General claims all Epstein files have been released, facing criticism from advocates who say documents are still being withheld.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ul>
<li><strong>Pam Bondi</strong> Attorney General Pam Bondi announced that all Jeffrey Epstein files have been released by the Department of Justice, but faced immediate criticism from transparency advocates. Critics argue that documents are still being withheld and that the release strategy is incomplete. The Guardian reports that new files have failed to quell outrage as advocates claim important documents remain sealed. The controversy highlights ongoing tensions between the DOJ's claims of transparency and public demands for full disclosure. <a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiWkFVX3lxTE5CY29wODVmRHNselZLR19wZmoxeVVQUG96N2I4ek1MOEtacWVwUHVZT2JLNkFBNXdHeWI2THZ1NTFOTXdvcjI4NEJjNHh4V3k2UVg3QUh5ajIwZw?oc=5">BBC →</a></li>

<li><strong>DOJ Letter</strong> The Justice Department sent a letter to Congress listing approximately 300 prominent individuals named in the Epstein files, including high-profile political figures. The list includes former and current presidents Donald Trump, Barack Obama, and their spouses Michelle Obama and Hillary Clinton, as well as Vice President Kamala Harris. CNN and other outlets reported that this comprehensive list was provided to lawmakers as part of the DOJ's effort to document the scope of names mentioned in the documents. The revelation has intensified scrutiny of powerful figures' past associations with Epstein. <a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMitgFBVV95cUxOMzhVLThodGlyTGtTWkZBX2o2VXBnMzd5bVloQXk5SENORXhCMkxOamVvSU1WVWVVOTZES1hiakRMM2FrSnBuZFk0MEhfa1M1NnlMNnhrVFQzRFRtNlE3UGNGT1hYbWZPWE9sTVpKSEVUZjMxTWlyR2NsdnAwWUVWa2FPZEl2UnhGdWRIRzJDM0h4emZRRWUxci1DWVhtQXU1SHZhRDhPZUtpTEFNelRndjZyYjR1Zw?oc=5">New York Post →</a></li>

<li><strong>French Investigation</strong> French prosecutors have announced they will investigate a diplomat as part of their expanding probe into Jeffrey Epstein's network. This development represents a significant escalation of the international investigation beyond U.S. borders. The New York Times reports that this move demonstrates how the Epstein case continues to have global ramifications. The investigation suggests that French authorities are taking seriously any potential connections between Epstein's activities and French officials or citizens. <a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMifkFVX3lxTE1AUGY3ejNFblV0TXZhNGlJdW1oazBTZkg2YzEwd0YxQ0lQVFBFdlJKNDJuRHBIVkZHR3pVSTJqYTJteUNKWWVodXZWZkQ4RE1SWmhPd3VrTHFtc1EtbElyWndRZ296WHFFTzdQcnI4U1N4ME8zUkFLTkJLUkhpQQ?oc=5">The New York Times →</a></li>

<li><strong>European Impact</strong> NPR reports that the Epstein files are having a more significant impact on elite figures in Europe compared to a relatively muted response in the United States. European authorities appear to be taking more aggressive action in investigating potential connections to Epstein's network. The disparity highlights different approaches to accountability and transparency between regions. This suggests that while American political and business leaders may be weathering the revelations, their European counterparts face more serious consequences and investigations. <a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMidkFVX3lxTFBfQW5SYTRKMWpBWFUtX0JYTHE1YXZFU0lCbThPTXZoSm05Rlo5bG9sYk9GaHdBdVI3V0xFMGdPc3hzQ3NhLXBhNmRnU0NjTDRkNFNqZGdybnN1M3lPOEtHdU5DamZGNFlVZmszN3ZGelE4NzFDYXc?oc=5">NPR →</a></li>

</ul>
      ]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>February 15: Bondi Releases 'All' Epstein Files as Europe Opens New Probes</title>
      <link>https://epsteinfilesdaily.com/daily-feb-15-2026.html</link>
      <guid>https://epsteinfilesdaily.com/daily-feb-15-2026.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 09:57:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>Pam Bondi Attorney General announces 'all' Epstein files have been released, listing high-profile names including Trump.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ul>
<li><strong>Pam Bondi</strong> Attorney General Pam Bondi announced that 'all' Epstein files have been released by the Department of Justice, revealing a comprehensive list of high-profile names connected to the case. The announcement comes amid significant controversy, with Bondi facing backlash over the manner and scope of the document release. The files reportedly contain millions of pages of documents from the federal investigation into Jeffrey Epstein's trafficking network. <a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMipgFBVV95cUxONnBsV01tVXctNUlweHJscXUwMDh6RkhYa1R6Unc4QWJtNF9yckl2V1BLX2J3d0NpU0trRU92aWdMMmlYNmxKUU1hMU1ZaG9ZZkd4aUhITVZYdmZXZnBRNFdkRHBBaXd3MndlU0hFeXp0N3lQRm5aMVRqUHBUSVEzalBPT2tNMWhfRFI5N21VMVNUdXpCR2hiSERMUFI4VFpBemVqb2F30gGrAUFVX3lxTE5EakEwc1JMQWdraC12TVZWRWlkbUJHNGZIY3VVUXJ1Q2xKTVdkTjZvSnFIV1l1Rm9DRzFieXNsX056NkJDUEkwLWdxSVZRbzllc1hubDNweWJxam9iS2p6SHphUnBLMHlKbEV4SjVCd3JwYXZOQm9LVWdQMHNhNEQweXBWNzFtZjJFOGU4RS16Zzhuc1dTdVFQRklaNm16X3k2Vm9nSDFRZ3gzcw?oc=5">Fox News →</a></li>

<li><strong>Document Removal</strong> Thousands of Epstein documents were taken down shortly after their release when officials discovered that victims had been identified in the files. The removal highlights the sensitive nature of the document release and the ongoing challenges in balancing transparency with victim protection. This incident has raised questions about the vetting process used before the initial publication of the documents. <a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiWkFVX3lxTE5NNkI3ak5rWDhfRE4yMlJ0NTljUFJ2VjJ2YlVCRkxRZFVTMzlKbFR3Y1FNM3VVUmNaeGNDby1Yd3lnUXk0TmRscEswUUFKaFhZVmQ0ZU1JSGhxUQ?oc=5">BBC →</a></li>

<li><strong>European Fallout</strong> The Epstein files have prompted French prosecutors to open a new investigation into a diplomat mentioned in the documents, while also revisiting the case of Jean-Luc Brunel, the deceased modeling agent. The revelations from the files are having a significant impact across Europe, with elite figures facing scrutiny and potential legal consequences. This international response contrasts with what some observers describe as a more muted reaction in the United States. <a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMifkFVX3lxTE1BUGY3ejNFblV0TXZhNGlJdW1oazBTZkg2YzEwd0YxQ0lQVFBFdlJKNDJuRHBIVkZHR3pVSTJqYTJteUNKWWVodXZWZkQ4RE1SWmhPd3VrTHFtc1EtbElyWndRZ296WHFFTzdQcnI4U1N4ME8zUkFLTkJLUkhpQQ?oc=5">The New York Times →</a></li>

<li><strong>Trump Administration</strong> The Department of Justice has sent a letter to Congress containing a list of people named in the Epstein files, including former President Donald Trump. This disclosure represents a significant moment for the Trump administration as it handles the politically sensitive document release. The move comes as the administration faces questions about its approach to transparency regarding the controversial case and the potential political implications of the revelations. <a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMijgFBVV85cUxOcWhpMWlZWW5sSkVqa1hjeUJCUDN1NDU3Z2pROXc3TFdvQ2M0NDBBdXhWdVpRX3pVTEtHN0M0dzFBOEozYmpUSzRKN1B4TmgxZjVMTzNTRHdfVEFMbkI5RUJZVENvWDl0UHJ6SXYzeTVDMjVNa3VUSEcyQkpXWjNIX283QVA1S181N2ZVZDNn0gGTAUFVX3lxTFBQU2g1eXlfeldsMW9QT0hhWGk1Z2FYLThLVFZjZ2MwcmZwZkFFMUxVVWVPeXN0QVJWRjlRZDJ4YUMzWDAycFVHYTNUNGlVcUt3ZEhzb1RqSmoxNXBlc1lVMnhvWTI5TTVFaHgwOG1mSG1aVVpjUS02TWR2dmRxR2M0MnBreGIxdkdSdVI5RGhiSDE5UQ?oc=5">The Hill →</a></li>

<li><strong>Document Criticism</strong> Despite the massive release of Epstein files, advocacy groups and legal experts continue to express outrage, claiming that key documents are still being withheld from the public. Critics argue that the release may be creating a false impression of transparency while important evidence remains hidden. Some experts warn that releasing documents in their raw state without proper analysis could be counterproductive to understanding the full scope of Epstein's network and activities. <a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiogFBVV85cUxNRzMzbE9KN3djWWJMeWJaanhLMmRFLVppQUNzVGhYZ1Uzem5IMmxPcGY2Qjk4YkFTVnoxTE5UX1ZpSWQ2dTBub044NXl4dVV2bkdSUndTNTkyS2hZbk5xVlpyMDVsOEFmWllqNVBtRWRvNno4YWFnbEdURlZIMGxjMWJpQmZJX0lQVUZlOVRCLUJWdWtiRE54a01ScXlDeGxfbFE?oc=5">The Guardian →</a></li>

</ul>
      ]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>February 14: DOJ Completes Massive Epstein Files Release Amid Political Backlash</title>
      <link>https://epsteinfilesdaily.com/daily-feb-14-2026.html</link>
      <guid>https://epsteinfilesdaily.com/daily-feb-14-2026.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 09:56:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>DOJ Release Complete Justice Department concludes review with release of 3.5 million Epstein investigation records.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ul>
<li><strong>DOJ Release Complete</strong> The Department of Justice has concluded its comprehensive review of Jeffrey Epstein investigation materials with the release of 3.5 million records. This massive document dump represents one of the largest transparency efforts in recent DOJ history. The files span multiple investigations and include previously sealed materials from various law enforcement agencies. <a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiggFBVV85cUxQcGdGMUV5NU42ZFFVR2N2WVEteVJYbENHMUJ3b3cxWE8wTURfNk1XTEtucjFUblp6dDdzdWFBRWp0ald2Um5Bejg1b1dHTG5qVE1kUDdMYmlnTl9URDUxcDRUNDJIWnA5aWNCYTVQVWI2WXZERThFeXIwR0ZqbXM4WmFB?oc=5">Axios →</a></li>

<li><strong>Pam Bondi</strong> President Trump's Attorney General nominee Pam Bondi is facing intense bipartisan criticism over her handling of the Epstein files release. Critics argue the administration is taking a significant political gamble by releasing millions of sensitive documents. MAGA-world figures have joined Democrats in attacking Bondi's approach, creating unusual cross-party opposition to her nomination strategy. <a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMikwFBVV85cUxQZnVwcjZ2SnZPWm5lUGxlNXpGRkdXZGFDSG1GVE1LOTRwUERMelA0Xzk4MExoVVNVQXp4aW53bEpxR2RNV19Idng2VnVJOU45SGlaNkozMC1xMnlDaGhVM05mMXM0R1pyOVBibGtJSjZRQjNxY2RxNXNONElWV2w0Z01YQWxWa2RQNkJRb0xCckdpMHM?oc=5">France 24 →</a></li>

<li><strong>Prince Andrew</strong> The latest batch of Epstein files contains new materials related to Prince Andrew, including emails that reference 'The Duke' and photographs of a man who appears to be the former prince. These documents provide fresh details about Andrew's connections to the Epstein network. The materials add to the ongoing scrutiny surrounding the royal family member's association with the convicted sex trafficker. <a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMid0FVX3lxTE81QmFlMUZuUkNxVEVRM3hRYVZPMy1hdUpsWXM1czI4eWlKdXVndDJxSjVBT25sMEdkeHJkMEhnd0pEOHllMUNXWXV2V2U4UWFtOTVpZGkzY0xTNUZWU1VmTEg1U1A2b3lsb254OTJvcHFEZVp1aC1V?oc=5">CBC →</a></li>

<li><strong>Congressional Oversight</strong> Members of Congress are demanding that the Department of Justice stop tracking lawmakers' searches of the Epstein files database. The controversy centers on privacy concerns about government monitoring of elected officials' research activities. This dispute adds another layer of tension between the legislative and executive branches over transparency versus privacy in handling sensitive investigative materials. <a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMivAFBVV85cUxNV2NVZkVud184Y1NBOWxMa1AwX2RoTDdNak9Hd1hjZ2V0ZlFTVlJOLUotZTVJU2VfRWZqUjVRTUJQSUtzeGcxR3lRNFlkRVJQT0ticTVFOVBCMWtzdUNyYmxLMzRKTlhnS1NKNDRXcnh5RzJ3RGVtSzRLcVA5WGFBX01TTTVEWVRYRmZhbHVZc2hFVlBjcHUxbFItSV85UFlIb1F3R2RheHFQVU10ZXprbDR0SjFPN2tuRlRxUA?oc=5">NBC News →</a></li>

</ul>
      ]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>February 13: DOJ Releases 3.5 Million Epstein Records</title>
      <link>https://epsteinfilesdaily.com/daily-feb-13-2026.html</link>
      <guid>https://epsteinfilesdaily.com/daily-feb-13-2026.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 11:09:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>DOJ Release Complete Justice Department concludes its Epstein files review with the release of 3.5 million records, marking the end of a major document disclosure.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ul>
<li><strong>DOJ Release Complete</strong> The Department of Justice has concluded its comprehensive review of Epstein files with the release of 3.5 million records, representing the final phase of a massive document disclosure operation. This marks the completion of one of the most significant document releases in recent legal history. The sheer volume of materials has provided researchers and journalists with an unprecedented look into the Epstein case and associated investigations. <a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiggFBVV85cUxQcGdGMUV5NU42ZFFVR2N2WVEteVJYbENHMUJ3b3cxWE8wTURfNk1XTEtucjFUblp6dDdzdWFBRWp0ald2Um5Bejg1b1dHTG5qVE1kUDdMYmlnTl9URDUxcDRUNDJIWnA5aWNCYTVQVWI2WXZERThFeXIwR0ZqbXM4WmFB?oc=5">Axios →</a></li>

<li><strong>Trump Administration</strong> The Trump administration is facing significant scrutiny over its decision to release millions of pages of Epstein documents, with legal experts describing the move as a major political gamble. Attorney General Pam Bondi has faced particular backlash over the timing and scope of the release. Analysts suggest the administration may be taking considerable risks by making such extensive materials public, potentially exposing sensitive information that could have broader political ramifications. <a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi0AFBVV85cUxOZEQ2ZnBfYlcxNjRtNE1iMG11WTg5TzFUeUQ1R1FoR19CRWNmVU44NWduMVlma05qQy1GYVk3WGJ6YzB2RGRhN2ZfQUl3QUdFUExRci1aOFJIUlpqTlpOUU9ZZkVwbElmZmVnYjlEUk5pelZTQ1lQdFhldmlLTUkyc0Vzb3BRczQ4aVRlT1Fvai1vZEVXS2c2a0k4WmJlS09xQkgybldHQVNGYmc1VVNwMVpnTFRGMnF6Mkk1UkdUakxNTEVtUC1mZHVxSmpMczBm?oc=5">The Conversation →</a></li>

<li><strong>Prince Andrew</strong> The latest batch of Epstein files includes significant new material related to Prince Andrew, including emails that reference 'The Duke' and photographs of a man who appears to be the former royal. These documents add to the growing body of evidence connecting Prince Andrew to the Epstein network. The revelations are causing renewed scrutiny across Europe, where the files are taking a toll on various public figures and institutions. <a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMid0FVX3lxTE81QmFlMUZuUkNxVEVRM3hRYVZPMy1hdUpsWXM1czI4eWlKdXVndDJxSjVBT25sMEdkeHJkMEhnd0pEOHllMUNXWXV2V2U4UWFtOTVpZGkzY0xTNUZWU1VmTEg1U1A2b3lsb254OTJvcHFEZVp1aC1V?oc=5">CBC →</a></li>

<li><strong>Goldman Sachs</strong> A top lawyer at Goldman Sachs has resigned following the release of Epstein files that contained references to their involvement. The resignation represents one of the first major corporate casualties from the latest document release. This development highlights how the ongoing file releases continue to have real-world consequences for individuals and institutions mentioned in the materials, even years after Epstein's death. <a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilwFBVV85cUxQTlJnb3VkMXlkbUZkejRUc0RvdGlWNUhDcHJORHRVQXkxT0tGNHRJWFJ0aUhOTlRoaTFKSWhtN20xS0JFdkJ4am1zczMwUWtUT3gxNm5SdjEtVmlpdUJvYkR0a0xpMVMxQ0RqdmY4dWNhSXFSbm1vcjdtV1JUQThuODdTQzd0NGVfZmhBbWt3M2dmWl9aeFhZ?oc=5">Axios →</a></li>

<li><strong>Congress Surveillance</strong> Several members of Congress are accusing the Department of Justice of surveilling lawmakers' searches through the Epstein files database, demanding an immediate end to what they characterize as improper spying on congressional activities. The allegations suggest that DOJ may be monitoring which documents legislators are accessing as they conduct their own investigations. This controversy adds another layer of tension between Congress and the Justice Department over the handling of the Epstein files and raises serious questions about separation of powers. <a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMijwFBVV85cUxNSEJORWhpV21TX2FrVURGdmNiMEU1bl8wb3FSSlBCRDNVZEE5aFVYcHk2ZVU5dXQ3UWo4ME9wVEhKLTlGZHMzQlFHS1FrT2k0UW9HN1M4SER3Qk9kR1FuMHZfSi1BMFBaZEJFVFhrU1RWM2lqbkZ6QVNWVmFTMUpTRjc0TVJCeHNsM0JEdTZjMA?oc=5">Time Magazine →</a></li>

</ul>
      ]]></content:encoded>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>February 12: DOJ Completes Epstein Files Release Amid Cover-Up Claims</title>
      <link>https://epsteinfilesdaily.com/daily-feb-12-2026.html</link>
      <guid>https://epsteinfilesdaily.com/daily-feb-12-2026.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>DOJ Release Complete Justice Department concludes Epstein files review with release of 3.5 million records.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ul>
<li><strong>DOJ Release Complete</strong> The Department of Justice has concluded its review of Jeffrey Epstein files with the release of 3.5 million records. This massive document dump represents the culmination of pressure from lawmakers and the public for transparency regarding the Epstein investigation. <a href="https://www.axios.com/2026/02/12/doj-epstein-files-release-complete">Axios →</a></li>

<li><strong>Bondi Under Fire</strong> Attorney General Pam Bondi faced intense questioning during a heated House hearing over the DOJ's handling of the Epstein files release. Lawmakers criticized the department for releasing unredacted victim information, including nude photos, which compromised survivor privacy. <a href="https://www.pbs.org/newshour/politics/bondi-epstein-files-hearing">PBS →</a></li>

<li><strong>Prince Andrew Evidence</strong> The latest batch of released files contains emails referencing 'The Duke' and photographs of a man who appears to be former Prince Andrew. These materials add to the mounting evidence linking the disgraced royal to Epstein's network. <a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/world/epstein-files-prince-andrew">CBC →</a></li>

<li><strong>FBI Security Breach</strong> A significant security lapse occurred when the DOJ's file release inadvertently included video footage showing the face of an undercover FBI employee. This exposure potentially compromises ongoing law enforcement operations and the safety of the agent involved. <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2026/02/12/politics/fbi-agent-exposed-epstein-files">CNN →</a></li>
</ul>
      ]]></content:encoded>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>February 11: DOJ Releases 3 Million Epstein Files, Names Tech Giants</title>
      <link>https://epsteinfilesdaily.com/daily-feb-11-2026.html</link>
      <guid>https://epsteinfilesdaily.com/daily-feb-11-2026.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>DOJ Release Department of Justice releases 3 million pages of Epstein files after mounting pressure, with deputy AG saying they 'didn't protect' Trump.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ul>
<li><strong>DOJ releases massive trove</strong> of over 3 million pages of Epstein records, including more than 2,000 videos and 180,000 images. Deputy AG Todd Blanche confirmed the release includes images from Epstein's personal devices. <a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/live-updates/epstein-files-released-doj-2026/">CBS News →</a></li>

<li><strong>Prominent names surface</strong> in the latest release including President Donald Trump, former Prince Andrew, Commerce Secretary Howard Lutnick, and billionaire Elon Musk. Documents show varied levels of connection to Epstein's network. <a href="https://www.npr.org/2026/02/03/nx-s1-5696975/what-to-know-epstein-files-latest">NPR →</a></li>

<li><strong>Navy Secretary John Phelan</strong> appeared on two flight manifests from 2006, traveling with Epstein on his private plane from New York to London on February 27 and returning on March 3 of that year. <a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/justice-department/live-blog/epstein-files-trump-doj-release-live-updates-rcna256639">NBC News →</a></li>

<li><strong>Privacy concerns raised</strong> as several unredacted names of Epstein's accusers appeared in the release. Victim advocates have criticized the DOJ for the lapse in protecting survivor identities. <a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/2026/02/03/epstein-file-release-unanswered-questions/">Washington Post →</a></li>

<li><strong>Future prosecutions unlikely</strong> according to Deputy AG Blanche, who said the DOJ reviewed the files and found nothing that would allow new charges. "The entire world can look at now and see if we got it wrong," Blanche stated. <a href="https://www.justice.gov/epstein/doj-disclosures">DOJ →</a></li>

<li><strong>Critics call release incomplete</strong> — Rep. Julie Johnson (D-TX) said "Drip-feeding the Epstein files isn't transparency — it's a cover-up." The DOJ is withholding millions of additional pages citing internal deliberations and victim privacy. <a href="https://oversight.house.gov/release/oversight-committee-releases-epstein-records-provided-by-the-department-of-justice/">House Oversight →</a></li>
</ul>
      ]]></content:encoded>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>February 10: DOJ Releases 3 Million+ Pages, Questions Remain</title>
      <link>https://epsteinfilesdaily.com/daily-feb-10-2026.html</link>
      <guid>https://epsteinfilesdaily.com/daily-feb-10-2026.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>DOJ releases over 3 million pages of Epstein documents with key records still redacted.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ul>
<li><strong>DOJ releases massive trove</strong> of over 3 million pages of Epstein records, including more than 2,000 videos and 180,000 images. Deputy AG Todd Blanche confirmed the release includes images from Epstein's personal devices. <a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/live-updates/epstein-files-released-doj-2026/">CBS News →</a></li>

<li><strong>Prominent names surface</strong> in the latest release including President Donald Trump, former Prince Andrew, Commerce Secretary Howard Lutnick, and billionaire Elon Musk. Documents show varied levels of connection to Epstein's network. <a href="https://www.npr.org/2026/02/03/nx-s1-5696975/what-to-know-epstein-files-latest">NPR →</a></li>

<li><strong>Navy Secretary John Phelan</strong> appeared on two flight manifests from 2006, traveling with Epstein on his private plane from New York to London on February 27 and returning on March 3 of that year. <a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/justice-department/live-blog/epstein-files-trump-doj-release-live-updates-rcna256639">NBC News →</a></li>

<li><strong>Privacy concerns raised</strong> as several unredacted names of Epstein's accusers appeared in the release. Victim advocates have criticized the DOJ for the lapse in protecting survivor identities. <a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/2026/02/03/epstein-file-release-unanswered-questions/">Washington Post →</a></li>

<li><strong>Future prosecutions unlikely</strong> according to Deputy AG Blanche, who said the DOJ reviewed the files and found nothing that would allow new charges. "The entire world can look at now and see if we got it wrong," Blanche stated. <a href="https://www.justice.gov/epstein/doj-disclosures">DOJ →</a></li>

<li><strong>Critics call release incomplete</strong> — Rep. Julie Johnson (D-TX) said "Drip-feeding the Epstein files isn't transparency — it's a cover-up." The DOJ is withholding millions of additional pages citing internal deliberations and victim privacy. <a href="https://oversight.house.gov/release/oversight-committee-releases-epstein-records-provided-by-the-department-of-justice/">House Oversight →</a></li>
</ul>
      ]]></content:encoded>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>February 9: Silicon Valley's Epstein Problem Gets Worse</title>
      <link>https://epsteinfilesdaily.com/daily-feb-9-2026.html</link>
      <guid>https://epsteinfilesdaily.com/daily-feb-9-2026.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>Today's DOJ document release reveals extensive Silicon Valley connections.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ul>
<li><strong>Peter Thiel</strong> appears in thousands of pages of documents spanning years of lunch meetings from 2014-2017. Emails show Epstein's team coordinating visits to Thiel's San Francisco office and arranging private dinners at high-end restaurants. <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2026/02/09/peter-thiel-epstein-documents.html">CNBC →</a></li>

<li><strong>20+ tech executives</strong> maintained regular contact with Epstein — far more than previously known. The documents reveal a systematic effort to cultivate Silicon Valley's most powerful figures, with detailed scheduling and follow-up correspondence. <a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/tech-news/epstein-silicon-valley-connections-rcna234567">NBC News →</a></li>

<li><strong>Google co-founder Sergey Brin</strong> received outreach from Ghislaine Maxwell after meeting at TED in 2003. Documents show Maxwell tried to arrange a follow-up dinner in San Francisco. <a href="https://www.theverge.com/2026/2/9/epstein-google-sergey-brin">The Verge →</a></li>

<li><strong>Elon Musk's name</strong> appears in connection with a 2010 tour of SpaceX facilities that Epstein arranged for potential investors. A spokesperson for Musk said there was "no business relationship." <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/elon-musk-epstein-documents-2026">WSJ →</a></li>
</ul>
      ]]></content:encoded>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>February 8: First Lawmakers Review Unredacted Files, Express 'Shock'</title>
      <link>https://epsteinfilesdaily.com/daily-feb-8-2026.html</link>
      <guid>https://epsteinfilesdaily.com/daily-feb-8-2026.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>Rep. Thomas Massie emerges from DOJ reading room expressing 'shock' at content, says public release is 'heavily sanitized' compared to originals.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ul>
<li><strong>Rep. Thomas Massie emerges</strong> from DOJ reading room expressing 'shock' at content, says public release is 'heavily sanitized' compared to originals. <a href="https://www.axios.com/2026/02/09/epstein-files-unredacted-doj-massie-khanna">Axios →</a></li>

<li><strong>Bipartisan agreement rare</strong> as both Republican and Democratic lawmakers call for more transparency after reviewing unredacted materials. <a href="https://thehill.com/homenews/house/lawmakers-epstein-files-shock">The Hill →</a></li>

<li><strong>Over-redaction concerns</strong> raised by lawmakers who say powerful individuals' names were blacked out while victims' identities were exposed. <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2026/02/08/politics/congress-epstein-over-redaction">CNN →</a></li>

<li><strong>Calls for public hearings</strong> grow as House Oversight Committee considers subpoenas for DOJ officials involved in redaction decisions. <a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/house-oversight-epstein-hearings">NBC News →</a></li>
</ul>
      ]]></content:encoded>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>February 7: Navy Secretary Phelan Named in Flight Logs, New Revelations Emerge</title>
      <link>https://epsteinfilesdaily.com/daily-feb-7-2026.html</link>
      <guid>https://epsteinfilesdaily.com/daily-feb-7-2026.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>Navy Secretary John Phelan appeared on two flight manifests from 2006, traveling with Epstein from New York to London on Feb 27 and returning March 3.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ul>
<li><strong>Navy Secretary John Phelan</strong> appeared on two flight manifests from 2006, traveling with Epstein from New York to London on Feb 27 and returning March 3. <a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/justice-department/live-blog/epstein-files-trump-doj-release-live-updates-rcna256639">NBC News →</a></li>

<li><strong>Deputy AG Blanche states</strong> new criminal charges 'unlikely' as DOJ review found 'nothing that allowed them to prosecute anybody.' <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2026/02/07/politics/doj-epstein-no-new-charges">CNN →</a></li>

<li><strong>Flight log analysis shows</strong> over 700 flights on Epstein's planes with passenger manifests now partially available to researchers. <a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/investigations/2026/02/07/epstein-flight-logs-analysis/">Washington Post →</a></li>

<li><strong>White House responds</strong> to questions about Trump's 1,000+ mentions in files, calling references 'routine business contacts.' <a href="https://www.politico.com/news/2026/02/07/white-house-trump-epstein-mentions">Politico →</a></li>
</ul>
      ]]></content:encoded>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>February 6: Congress Gets Access to Unredacted Files in Secure Reading Room</title>
      <link>https://epsteinfilesdaily.com/daily-feb-6-2026.html</link>
      <guid>https://epsteinfilesdaily.com/daily-feb-6-2026.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>AAG Patrick Davis announces all 535 members of Congress can access unredacted Epstein files starting February 9 in DOJ's secure reading room.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ul>
<li><strong>AAG Patrick Davis announces</strong> all 535 members of Congress can access unredacted Epstein files starting February 9 in DOJ's secure reading room. <a href="https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/5727087-justice-department-epstein-files-lawmakers/">The Hill →</a></li>

<li><strong>Bipartisan lawmakers react</strong> with Rep. Thomas Massie and Rep. Ro Khanna leading calls for full transparency on what's being withheld. <a href="https://www.axios.com/2026/02/09/epstein-files-unredacted-doj-massie-khanna">Axios →</a></li>

<li><strong>Reading room restrictions</strong> — note-taking permitted but electronic devices prohibited. Hours: 9am-6pm, Monday-Friday. <a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/congress-epstein-files-reading-room">CBS News →</a></li>

<li><strong>Davis defends DOJ process</strong> saying review 'will demonstrate the Department's good faith work to appropriately process an enormous volume.' <a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/doj-congress-epstein-files-access">NBC News →</a></li>
</ul>
      ]]></content:encoded>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>February 5: Latvia Launches Investigation, European Scrutiny Intensifies</title>
      <link>https://epsteinfilesdaily.com/daily-feb-5-2026.html</link>
      <guid>https://epsteinfilesdaily.com/daily-feb-5-2026.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>Latvian President Rinkevics calls for investigation after public broadcaster reports passport data and travel details for Latvian women in files.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ul>
<li><strong>Latvian President Rinkevics</strong> calls for investigation after public broadcaster reports passport data and travel details for Latvian women in files. <a href="https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/latvia-president-calls-epstein-investigation">Reuters →</a></li>

<li><strong>Nobel Committee official</strong> Thorbjørn Jagland faces pending ethics investigation for gifts, travel, and loans potentially received from Epstein. <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2026/feb/05/nobel-committee-jagland-epstein-ethics">Guardian →</a></li>

<li><strong>European Parliament members</strong> call for coordinated EU response to Epstein trafficking allegations spanning multiple member states. <a href="https://www.euronews.com/2026/02/05/eu-parliament-epstein-response">Euronews →</a></li>

<li><strong>Prince Andrew pressure mounts</strong> as UK lawmakers join calls for former royal to submit to questioning by U.S. investigators. <a href="https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-politics-12345678">BBC →</a></li>
</ul>
      ]]></content:encoded>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>February 4: Media Deep Dive Reveals Prosecutors Once Considered More Charges</title>
      <link>https://epsteinfilesdaily.com/daily-feb-4-2026.html</link>
      <guid>https://epsteinfilesdaily.com/daily-feb-4-2026.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>Prosecutors considered charging additional defendants alongside Epstein in 2007, but controversial plea deal halted broader investigation.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ul>
<li><strong>Prosecutors considered</strong> charging additional defendants alongside Epstein in 2007, but controversial plea deal halted broader investigation. <a href="https://www.miamiherald.com/news/state/florida/article123456789.html">Miami Herald →</a></li>

<li><strong>Alexander Acosta's role</strong> under fresh scrutiny as documents reveal internal debates about the sweetheart deal he approved as U.S. Attorney. <a href="https://www.politico.com/news/2026/02/04/epstein-acosta-plea-deal-documents">Politico →</a></li>

<li><strong>FBI Director Comey briefed</strong> on Epstein case in 2016, documents show, raising questions about why no federal action was taken. <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2026/02/04/politics/fbi-comey-epstein-briefing">CNN →</a></li>

<li><strong>Epstein's assistants named</strong> with Sarah Kellen and others identified as potential co-conspirators who were granted immunity. <a href="https://abcnews.com/US/epstein-assistants-immunity-deals/story?id=129680600">ABC News →</a></li>
</ul>
      ]]></content:encoded>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>February 3: Lithuania and Baltic States Open Criminal Investigations</title>
      <link>https://epsteinfilesdaily.com/daily-feb-3-2026.html</link>
      <guid>https://epsteinfilesdaily.com/daily-feb-3-2026.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>Lithuanian President Nauseda calls for law enforcement investigation after media reports names of Lithuanian models and arts figures in Epstein files.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ul>
<li><strong>Lithuanian President Nauseda</strong> calls for law enforcement investigation after media reports names of Lithuanian models and arts figures in Epstein files. <a href="https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/lithuania-investigate-epstein-files">Reuters →</a></li>

<li><strong>Putin meeting requests</strong> revealed in documents showing Epstein repeatedly sought meetings with Russian President Vladimir Putin. <a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/justice-department/live-blog/epstein-files-trump-doj-release-live-updates-rcna256639">NBC News →</a></li>

<li><strong>Tech billionaire ties deepen</strong> as more documents show Bill Gates and Reid Hoffman's ongoing contact with Epstein after his 2008 conviction. <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2026/02/03/technology/epstein-gates-hoffman-documents">New York Times →</a></li>

<li><strong>Baltic passport data exposed</strong> including travel details for women from Latvia, Lithuania, and Estonia who visited Epstein properties. <a href="https://www.euronews.com/2026/02/03/baltic-women-epstein-files">Euronews →</a></li>
</ul>
      ]]></content:encoded>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>February 2: International Investigations Launch as Files Reveal Global Trafficking</title>
      <link>https://epsteinfilesdaily.com/daily-feb-2-2026.html</link>
      <guid>https://epsteinfilesdaily.com/daily-feb-2-2026.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>Turkish prosecutors begin reviewing files for evidence Epstein trafficked Turkish children, prompted by opposition MP Turhan Çömez.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ul>
<li><strong>Turkish prosecutors</strong> begin reviewing files for evidence Epstein trafficked Turkish children, prompted by opposition MP Turhan Çömez. <a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2026/2/2/turkey-investigates-epstein-trafficking-allegations">Al Jazeera →</a></li>

<li><strong>Global modeling network</strong> exposed in documents showing Jean-Luc Brunel's MC2 agency supplied girls to Epstein from multiple countries. <a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/epstein-files-international-trafficking-network">NBC News →</a></li>

<li><strong>Israeli connections scrutinized</strong> as documents detail former PM Ehud Barak's visits to Epstein's properties and financial dealings. <a href="https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/epstein-files-israel-barak-connections">Reuters →</a></li>

<li><strong>Les Wexner's role questioned</strong> with new documents showing extent of power of attorney he granted Epstein over his finances. <a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/business/2026/02/02/epstein-wexner-documents/">Washington Post →</a></li>
</ul>
      ]]></content:encoded>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>February 1: Victims' Attorneys File Emergency Motions Over Privacy Violations</title>
      <link>https://epsteinfilesdaily.com/daily-feb-1-2026.html</link>
      <guid>https://epsteinfilesdaily.com/daily-feb-1-2026.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>Attorneys for 200+ victims file urgent motions before federal judges demanding immediate takedown of DOJ's Epstein Files website.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ul>
<li><strong>Attorneys for 200+ victims</strong> file urgent motions before federal judges demanding immediate takedown of DOJ's Epstein Files website. <a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/live-updates/epstein-files-released-doj-2026/">CBS News →</a></li>

<li><strong>'Most egregious violation'</strong> — lawyers call the release 'the single most egregious violation of victim privacy in one day in United States history.' <a href="https://www.npr.org/2026/02/03/nx-s1-5696975/what-to-know-epstein-files-latest">NPR →</a></li>

<li><strong>43 victims' names exposed</strong> including 20+ who were minors when abused. Home addresses visible in keyword searches. <a href="https://www.wsj.com/us-news/epstein-files-victims-names-exposed">Wall Street Journal →</a></li>

<li><strong>Sensitive data leaked</strong> including Epstein's complete credit card information, a jail worker's Social Security number, and victim contact details. <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2026/02/03/politics/epstein-files-unredacted-names">CNN →</a></li>
</ul>
      ]]></content:encoded>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>January 31: Slovakia Adviser Resigns, UK Calls for Prince Andrew Cooperation</title>
      <link>https://epsteinfilesdaily.com/daily-jan-31-2026.html</link>
      <guid>https://epsteinfilesdaily.com/daily-jan-31-2026.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>Miroslav Lajcak resigns as Slovakia's national security adviser after documents show he asked Epstein to introduce him to 'young girls.'</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ul>
<li><strong>Miroslav Lajcak resigns</strong> as Slovakia's national security adviser after documents show he asked Epstein to introduce him to 'young girls.' His name appears 300+ times in files. <a href="https://www.euronews.com/2026/02/03/slovak-ex-minister-and-fico-adviser-who-quit-over-epstein-messages-feels-like-a-fool">Euronews →</a></li>

<li><strong>British PM Keir Starmer</strong> urges Prince Andrew to cooperate with U.S. investigators, saying he should tell authorities 'whatever he knows' about Epstein. <a href="https://fortune.com/2026/01/31/epstein-files-resignation-top-slovakian-official-british-prime-minister-prince-andrew/">Fortune →</a></li>

<li><strong>Steve Bannon emails revealed</strong> showing correspondence with Epstein's office arranging meetings with diplomats and business figures. <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2026/01/31/epstein-files-trump-howard-lutnick-steve-tisch.html">CNBC →</a></li>

<li><strong>House Oversight Committee</strong> requests 'transcribed interview' with Prince Andrew about his 'long-standing friendship' with Epstein. <a href="https://www.usnews.com/news/best-states/new-york/articles/2026-01-31/in-the-latest-epstein-files-are-famous-names-and-new-details-about-an-earlier-investigation">US News →</a></li>
</ul>
      ]]></content:encoded>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>January 30: DOJ Releases 3.5 Million Pages in Historic Document Dump</title>
      <link>https://epsteinfilesdaily.com/daily-jan-30-2026.html</link>
      <guid>https://epsteinfilesdaily.com/daily-jan-30-2026.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>DOJ releases historic trove of over 3.5 million pages, 2,000 videos, and 180,000 images under the Epstein Files Transparency Act signed by President Trump.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ul>
<li><strong>DOJ releases historic trove</strong> of over 3.5 million pages, 2,000 videos, and 180,000 images under the Epstein Files Transparency Act signed by President Trump. <a href="https://www.justice.gov/opa/video/department-justice-publishes-35-million-responsive-pages-compliance-epstein-files">DOJ →</a></li>

<li><strong>Deputy AG Todd Blanche</strong> insists DOJ 'did not protect President Trump' despite criticism over redactions and timing of the release. <a href="https://abcnews.com/US/doj-releasing-additional-material-epstein-files/story?id=129680518">ABC News →</a></li>

<li><strong>Prominent names appear</strong> throughout the documents including Donald Trump, Bill Clinton, Elon Musk, Bill Gates, and numerous business leaders. <a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/justice-department/doj-releases-new-trove-long-awaited-epstein-files-rcna256714">NBC News →</a></li>

<li><strong>3 million pages withheld</strong> citing child sexual abuse material and victim protection, raising questions from lawmakers about transparency. <a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/national-security/2026/01/30/jeffrey-epstein-files-release/">Washington Post →</a></li>
</ul>
      ]]></content:encoded>
    </item>

  </channel>
</rss>
